

BART GYSEN

• PERSONAL DETIALS •

Oude Liersebaan 113 2220 Heist-op-den-Berg 0471416082

bart-gysen@hotmail.com

Date / place of birth

19/09/1991

Maaseik

Nationality

Belgian

Driving license

B, C

• LINKS •

<u>LinkedIn</u> Github

<u>Portfolio</u>

• REFERENCES •

Peter Van Grieken – Project Leader
Dekimo Turnhout
peter.vangrieken@dekimo.com
+32473452804

• PERSONAL SKILLS •

Go-getter

Teamplayer

Independent

Eager to learn

Creative

Flexibel

Enthusiastic

LANGUAGES

Dutch

English

PROFILE

After graduating and working for 10 years as an electrician in both domestic and industrial environments, I wanted to follow my passion and started studying Internet of Things at Thomas More in Geel. In addition to a focus on software development in C and Python, we covered several technologies during the course, including working with microcontrollers, single board computers, Linux and more.

As part of my studies, I carried out a number of projects to put my knowledge to the test. This included a project to read an energy meter using Modbus. The application/firmware would sent all the data to the data analysis tool using Debian for cross-compiling and remote debugging. I also did a project to read a thermostat using MQTT and another to learn FreeRTOS.

As an internship at Dekimo, I researched the new Matter protocol and built a controller that controls a game via Matter.

You can find these projects on my GitHub account.

* TECHNICAL SKILLS

C/C++ Low-level communication protocols (e.g.

SPI, I2C, UART)

Python

Modbus Linux

IIUX

MQTT

MS SQL

FreeRTOS

Networking

Logic Analyzer

HTML5

Oscilloscope

EDUCATION

Graduate Internet of Things (Embedded Software development), Thomas More Kempen, Geel

januari 2021 — June 2024

Electric Installations, GITHO, Nijlen

2008 — 2010

Electric Installations, T.I.M, Maasmechelen

2004 — 2007

∘ HOBBIES ∘

I enjoy working with computers and electronics, and I love turning my house into a smart home.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Internship R&D (Embedded Software), Dekimo, Turnhout

September 2023 — June 2024

Learn about the new Matter protocol and include it into a demo to attract an audience at trade shows.

Service technician, Alertis, Lummen

April 2022 — Today

Maintenance, repair and installation of automatic fire and gas protection systems.

Technician electricity, Unit-T, Mechelen

October 2021 — April 2022

Installation of new digital electricity and gas meters.

Technician electricity, Electro Zwijsen, Duffel

March 2021 — October 2021

Perform minor and major modifications to electrical installations, primarily in office buildings.

Technician high voltage electricity, Telcom, Hulshout

May 2016 — March 2021

Performing electrical work in and around high voltage cabinets.

Technician electricity, Goosens Electro, Hulshout

November 2015 — April 2016

Perform electrical work in the construction of new home and in renovation projects.

Technician high voltage electricity, Telcom, Hulshout

April 2011 — October 2015

Performing electrical work in and around high voltage cabinets.

Interim jobs

September 2010 — April 2011

Interim jobs in production and warehouses